New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Photograph Collection
© 2004 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: 1955 Flood
  - Housatonic River Bridge, New Milford (Box 4:, Other 57)
  - Cornwall Bridge (Box 4:, Other 58)
  - Thomaston (Box 4:, Other 59)
  - North of Beacon Falls (Box 4:, Other 60)
  - Beacon Falls (Box 4:, Other 61)
  - Farmington River, Farmington (Box 4:, Other 62)
  - Derby Junction (Box 4:, Other 63)
  - Junction Watertown Branch (Box 4:, Other 64)
  - Derby Junction (Box 4:, Other 65-66)
  - Ansonia-Derby (Box 4:, Other 67)
  - South of Beacon Falls (Box 4:, Other 68)
  - Naugatuck (Box 4:, Other 69)
  - Seymour (Box 4:, Other 70)
  - Collinsville (Box 4:, Other 71)
  - Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 72-73)
  - Devon (Box 4:, Other 74)
  - Beacon Falls (Box 4:, Other 75)
  - Seymour (Box 4:, Other 76)
  - Bank Street Junction, Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 77)
  - North of Ansonia (Box 4:, Other 78)
  - Winsted Line (Box 4:, Other 79)
  - Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 80)
  - Housatonic River Bridge, New Milford (Box 4:, Other 81)
  - Weatogue (Box 4:, Other 82)
  - Farmington River, Farmington (Box 4:, Other 83)
  - North of Plainville (Box 4:, Other 84)
  - Granby (Box 4:, Other 85)
  - South of Cornwall Bridge (Box 4:, Other 86)
  - Granby (Box 4:, Other 87)
  - North of Simsbury (Box 4:, Other 88)
  - Simsbury (Box 4:, Other 89-90)
  - Cornwall Bridge (Box 4:, Other 91)
  - Boardmans Bridge, New Milford (Box 4:, Other 92)
  - Housatonic River Bridge, New Milford (Box 4:, Other 93)
  - Farmington River, Farmington (Box 4:, Other 94)
  - North of Plainville (Box 4:, Other 95-96)
  - Housatonic River Bridge, New Milford (Box 4:, Other 97-99)
  - Cornwall Bridge (Box 4:, Other 100)
  - North of Plainville (Box 4:, Other 101)
  - Between Cornwall Bridge, West Cornwall (Box 4:, Other 102)
  - Hoslins (Box 4:, Other 103)
  - North of Plainville (Box 4:, Other 104)
  - Derby Junction (Box 4:, Other 105)
  - Seymour (Box 4:, Other 106)
  - Sheffield (Box 4:, Other 107)
  - Seymour (Box 4:, Other 108-109)
  - Derby (Box 4:, Other 110-112)
  - Sheffield (Box 4:, Other 113)
  - Derby (Box 4:, Other 114)
  - Unidentified (Box 4:, Other 115)
  - Sheffield (Box 4:, Other 116)
  - Seymour (Box 4:, Other 117)
  - Unidentified (Box 4:, Other 118)
  - Sheffield (Box 4:, Other 119)
  - Seymour (Box 4:, Other 120)
  - Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 121-122)
  - Naugatuck (Box 4:, Other 123)
  - Derby (Box 4:, Other 124)
  - Seymour (Box 4:, Other 125)
  - Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 126)
  - Freight House, Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 127)
  - Bank Street, Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 128)
  - Naugatuck (Box 4:, Other 129)
  - Bank Street, Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 130)
  - Freight House, Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 131)
  - Naugatuck (Box 4:, Other 132)
  - Sheffield (Box 4:, Other 133-134)
  - Seymour (Box 4:, Other 135)
  - Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 136)
  - Bank Street, Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 137)
  - Naugatuck (Box 4:, Other 138)
  - Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 139)
  - Naugatuck (Box 4:, Other 140)
  - Bank Street, Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 141)
  - Waterbury (Box 4:, Other 142)
  - Sheffield (Box 4:, Other 143)
  - Derby Junction (Box 4:, Other 144)
  - West Cornwall (Box 4:, Other 145)
  - Canann (Box 4:, Other 146)
  - Derby Junction (Box 4:, Other 147)
  - West Cornwall (Box 4:, Other 148)
  - Derby Junction (Box 4:, Other 149)
  - Derby (Box 4:, Other 150)
  - Sheffield (Box 4:, Other 151)
  - Derby (Box 4:, Other 152)
  - Canaan (Box 4:, Other 153)
  - Derby Junction (Box 4:, Other 154-157)
  - West Cornwall (Box 4:, Other 158)
  - Derby Junction (Box 4:, Other 159)
  - Derby Junction (Box 4:, Other 160-161)
  - West Cornwall (Box 4:, Other 162)
  - Farmington (Box 4:, Other 163-165)
  - Farmington River, Farmington (Box 4:, Other 166)
  - Unidentified (Box 4:, Other 167)
  - Farmington River, Farmington (Box 4:, Other 168)
  - Unidentified (Box 4:, Other 169)
  - Farmington (Box 4:, Other 170)
  - Windsor Locks (Box 4:, Other 171-172)
  - Farmington River, Farmington (Box 4:, Other 173)
  - Windsor Locks (Box 4:, Other 174)
  - Unidentified (Box 4:, Other 175)
  - Falls Village (Box 4:, Other 176-181)